Hey, Ningle.
We're sure Wang Wenhao was in that car.
He's at the human experiment factory now.
Could he be luring us there on purpose?
Ningle, call the police first.
Gu Yuan and I are heading there now.
Let's go.
Wang Wenhao
Ren Feifan and Gu Yuan
won't let you leave the country.
Otherwise, the Gu Family will impose
economic sanctions on my family.
This time,
there's really nothing I can do for you.
Sinai, don't you forget.
Hello.
The number you dialed is busy.
The number you dialed is powered off.
Please try again later.
Ren Feifan.
If you want me dead,
I'll take you down with me.
Ren Feifan
You sure took your sweet time.
Wang Wenhao
You've got nowhere left to run.
I've already called the police.
Ren Feifan, you're such a coward!
Hiding here, waiting for the cops?
If you've got guts,
come out and fight me one-on-one!
Do you dare?
Ren Feifan!
Come out here!
Ren Feifan
We all grew up together,
but I never took any of you seriously.
Since I was a kid, I've known
North City would eventually belong to me,
Wang Wenhao.
And you'd only have two fates:
First,
be my lackeys.
Second,
die by my hands.
But I, Wang Wenhao, never imagined
I'd be defeated by a woman.
You weren't defeated by a woman.
You were defeated by your own hands.
Fine.
Since you put it that way,
then let's have a showdown.
A showdown between men.
Cut the drama.
So what if it's two on one?
Come at me, both of you!
Let's make it two on one then.
Come on!
Bring it!
Fake my death?
Yeah.
Have him fake his death.
What's the big deal?
Sit, sit, sit down.
Listen to me.
Ruo Jin's dissociative identity disorder,
it stems from the traumatic stress
four years ago.
We need to recreate the same scenario,
to give her the same intense shock again.
Fight poison with poison.
Then we give her the chance to save you.
That way, it counts as her atonement.
Guilt and grievances cancel out,
and her trauma is resolved.
Only then is it possible
to pull her out of her split personality.
Jiang Ningle,
will this lousy idea even work?
Don't end up failing to save one,
and dragging the other down too.
Oh, just shut up.
It's called Cognitive Behavioral Therapy.
It helps patients
correct cognitive distortions.
If you think it works, then let's do it.
As long as it helps Ruo Jin recover,
I'm willing to take any risk.
Are you insane?
Are you crazy?
I've got a condition,
I'm afraid of heights, man!
You're afraid of heights
and you brought me here?
Well, duh, isn't it for the act?
It's only the third floor
and you're terrified.
Any higher and I'd be on my knees.
No wonder you didn't take me up higher.
Are you guys even reliable?
Where's Gu Yuan?
You don't trust me?
What's the rush?
Let poor Gu Yuan act a bit more.
It's not our turn yet.
What a sin.
Ruo Jin, come with me.
What are you doing?
Jiang Ningle and Ren Feifan
are having an affair at a hotel.
Come catch them in the act with me.
Gu Yuan, don't joke like that.
It's not funny at all.
It's true.
Let me tell you.
Back in college, this Jiang Ningle
already had a secret crush on Feifan.
Feifan didn't get a single visit request
from you for four years!
and it was all Jiang Ningle's doing.
Impossible. Absolutely impossible.
You're lying to me.
Come on, just come with me!
Let's go, let's go!
They're coming, they're coming!
Hurry up and tie me up!
I'm on it, I'm on it!
They're here, they're here!
Go, go, go!
Hold it up!
Hold it where?
Here, here, here!
Ruo Jin!
Feifan!
Four years ago, why didn't you save us?
Why didn't you save my parents?
Aren't you a doctor?
Aren't your medical skills unmatched?
Why didn't you save us?
Ningle, Ningle!
Just calm down.
Calm down!
Ruo Jin, don't come any closer! Run!
Okay, okay.
That day four years ago,
you clearly saw us.
I kept calling out to you,
but you did absolutely nothing.
Aren't you a doctor?
Where's your healer's heart?
Why do you get a cozy family life now?
Ningle!
Listen to me.
Four years ago,
four years ago, it was...
It was Wang Wenhao.
Wang Wenhao wanted to harm Feifan
and his family.
You know this.
If you want to blame someone, blame me.
Let Feifan go.
Take me instead, okay?
Stay back!
Ruo Jin!
Don't come any closer!
In your dreams! Go to hell!
Feifan!
Feifan, I've got you!
Ruo Jin, you caught me.
You saved me.
I've got you.
Ruo Jin, you caught me.
You saved me.
It's okay. It's all over now.
That scared the hell out of me!
I'm afraid of heights, you know!
I'll never do this job again,
no matter what!
You acted really well.
Of course.
I almost believed it myself.
Naturally.
Ruo Jin.
It's okay now.
Ugh, the stench of romance in the air.